Hello, I've been waiting quite some time for you actually.
No clue how long, I left my watch in the office.
I just thought I would personally ring you your phone back.
So before I give you it back, no, before I give you it back, I would like to discuss what you were taking in class and I would like to discuss what else was on there.
So before you take it, let's...
Aren't you rather handsome?
That's it, keep going.
Just enjoy this.
Remember, this is so you can get it out of your system and stop being such a pervert.
I know that's what you want.
That's it.
That's it, keep wanking for me.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
You want to stay a little more?
Mm.
Okay.
I said keep wanking.
Don't stop.
Just nice and slow.
That's much more comfortable.
I mean, I didn't really need these, did I?
This is what you really wanted to see.
Is it tidier than you expected?
Just right.
That's it, keep wanking.
Grip a little tighter.
That's better.
You've got nice strong hands, haven't you?
Do I look tasty?
Keep going.
That's it.
Nice long strokes.
You have to remember this view.
Really get a good look.
Don't take your eyes off me.
That's it.
Oh, that's it.
Yeah.
That's it.
Nice and close.
Look how good that looks.
I know you want to stick your face in there, don't you?
Have some self-control.
Asa.
Oh yes.
You're gonna come for me.
And then you're gonna sit down and delete all of those filthy pictures.
you so close no that's right I'm gonna let you come the deal's a deal I said get good long last look mmm now come all over that hand yeah and you know what because I'm so nice you can use my panties to clean up mmm and then when you